# 嗨喽大家好 我是王刚
Hello everyone this is Wang Gang
# 前段时间我们买了一套工程款的那个炉灶回来
Not too long ago we bought a commercial gas stove
# 今天我又买了一个工程款的冰箱
And today I bough a commercial refrigerator
# 这个冰箱四五百斤 宽也很宽
It weights 400-500 jin (200-250kg) and is pretty wide
# 跟我们屋头的不一样
Not quite the same as the one we have at home
# 肯定不一样哦 你那个好大哦
Surely it's not the same, the other one is not the same size
# 然后这个好像能耗也比你那个高
And this one uses more electricity than the other one
# 肯定撒 你冻的东西都比较多按
For sure, this one has a larger storage capacity
# 肯定那耗电量肯定大撒
It surely consumes more electricity
# 好 现在我们去看一下 去开箱
Alright let's go take a look and unbox it
# 走嘛
It's go
# 这钉子些取不取哦
Do we need to remove these nails?
# 钉子不取都要得 后头要留一部分留个那种（缝缝）出来
It doesn't matter, we need to leave a gap on the back
# 留个缝缝
Leave a gap
# 对 要留个缝缝
Yep leave a gap
# 不是它那个散不到热
Otherwise the heat can't get out
# 来嘛 （移）哈嘛四伯爷
Come let's move this Uncle
# 这个门朝这方移
Move it towards the door
# 都还好这个有轮子 不是的话（不好移）
Good that it has wheels, otherwise (is very difficult to move)
# 你朝门口扯撒
Pull it towards the door
# 这个没得轮子的话才懒得搞
It will be very difficult to move without these wheels
# 没得轮子害怕你够得干安
I doubt you can even move it without those wheels
# 等一哈等一哈 把那个胶纸取了多
Wait a minute, let's remove these wraps
# 我拿菜刀来割
I'll go get a knife
# 这根绳子要整了来
Cut this rope
# 这个拿得下来不
Can you take this off
# 拿得下来这个
We need to take this off
# 先把这个取了
First we take this off
# 卡起了 没得那么高的
It got stuck, I'm not tall enough
# 四伯爷 你更拿不到
Siboye you can't reach it
# 有啥子拿不到哦
What are you talking about?
# 这儿还有点卡起得
This bit got stuck
# 可以咯
Alrighty
# 这上面呢
What about up there
# 泡沫拿了就可以了
Take off those foam then that's it
# 不要慌四伯爷 我把这儿割了多
Hang on Siboye, let me cut this part first
# 这里都有点压烂了
This part is dented
# 这个是我们运输过程当中挤压到了
That happened during the delivery
# 这一点点没事 不影响使用
It doesn't matter, won't affect the usage
# 在路高头压到的啊
It got dented on the way?
# 哦哟 这里也遭压了
Crap this part is also dented
# 这个不关事 皮子上面有点压到不影响使用
It not a big deal, just on the shell. Won't affect the performance
# 主要是看它压缩机啊那个
As long as the compressor is working fine
# 这不美观的嘛
It doesn't look good
# 哎呀 这个东西实用就OK了
Well it's more about the functionality
# 你买的时候咋不跟他交涉呢 你包送包给我上下（货）
Why didn't you negotiate (with the seller) when you bought this? Ask them to take care of the shipment and delivery etc.?
# 你整坏了这些我要我都不要 你拿去换过
For example "If it's damaged, I won't sign off and you have to ship me a new one"
# 哎呀 将心比心
Well just put yourself in their shoes
# 我们看一下这个空间
Let's look at the space
# 这个的话唯一不好的是什么呢 它有声音
The only downside is the noise
# 这个压制机它有时候制冷的时候咕咕咕的响
Sometimes the compressor makes loud noise
# 有一点点声响 就比家用的要响一点
Just a little louder than a domestic one
# 估计有两米左右（高）
Roughly 2 meters in height
# 然后宽的话很宽
And it is pretty wide
# 耗电量的话也高
Electricity consumption is quite high
# 这个最好呢一个好处是什么呢
What's good about it is
# 就是空间大
It is spacious
# 可以放很多东西
It can accommodate lots of stuff
# 上面是保鲜 下面是急冻
Refrigerate on the top and freeze at the bottom
# 冻两三个（头）猪儿都冻得到
You can even put 2-3 pigs in there
# 两三个猪儿 可以哦
2-3 piglets, sure thing
# 这个冰柜很舒服 就是用起来很舒服
This refrigerator is handy to use
# 如果你们家人口比较多的话
If you have a big family
# 像我们家一家十多口人就适合用这种冰箱
Like us we have more than 10 people in our family
# 如果你们家三四个人五六个人的话就特别不适合
But if your family only has 3-6 people this wouldn't be your best option
# 这个的话就只适合怎么说呢酒店里面用
This is suitable for restaurants
# 还有我们这个冰箱不管是这种还是家里面用的
And another thing is these refrigerators, both domestic and commercial
# 拿回来都要放一段时间 放两三个小时再插电
You need to let it sit for 2-3 hours before plugging it in
# 然后这个冰箱它的价格是2400块钱
And this one cost about 2400 yuan
# 就价格来说的话比我们家用的便宜了不是一点点
Price wise it is a lot cheaper than domestic ones
# 家用的那个冰箱有几万的都有
Domestic refrigerators can cost up to tens of thousands
# 我见过最贵的几万
The most expensive one I've seen can cost tens of thousands
# 但是这个的话是非常实用的
But this is very practical
# 它除了能耗就是电量 耗电量高一点点之外
This only down side is it costs a little more on electricity
# 大坨一点之外没有其他什么缺点
And it's a little bulky, other than those it's great
# 还有我们这个冰箱靠墙放的话后面要有一点距离
Also we need to leave a small gap between the wall
# 不能够让它贴紧了 贴紧了没办法散热
If it sits too close to the wall, it won't cool down properly
# 朝里面移一点点
Move it in a little bit
# 好 要得了要得了
Alrighty, that will do
# 这个滚滚（轮子）你要固定一哈 拿个啥子东西来塞到
You need to find something to block the wheels
# 嗯塞哈 稍微塞哈就是
Yeah I will find something
# 不是它要到处跑 稍微哪样点
Otherwise it will roll all around the place
# 四伯爷你看嘛 这个冰箱就可以这样子关门
Look Uncle, you can close the fridge like this
# 你的就 你不敢这样子关
You can't to this to yours
# 看到没
Look
# 小心点 当真是新的是不哦
Careful, are you sure this is brand new?
# 不是 它就是那个个性晓得不嘛
Nah this is how it works
# 个性 金子做的都遭不住这样子整
It won't last long even if it's made from gold
# 金子做的就发（财）了
If it were made from gold I'll be so rich
# 那不是咋子安
Surely you will
# 好了 本期就给你们介绍到这里了
Alright this is the end of this video
# 随便啥子东西都要保护得好才得行
You need to cherish everything
# 保护得不好几家伙就整烂了
Otherwise you will break it not for long
# 是
Yes sir!
# 整烂了还是你的劳动成果去买
And then you will have to use your own work to pay for a new one
# 是 是这样子
Yes you are right
# 好了 本期视频到这里
Alright that's it
# 拜拜
Bye-bye